question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The main playable character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.",
         "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The ghosts in &quot;Pac-Man&quot; and &quot;Ms. Pac-Man&quot; have completely different behavior.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category":
             "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question":
             "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers":
             ["False"]}]}
